

Kluchko Michael

+7 (924) 200-84-73 • <u>slidenergy@gmail.com</u> 35 years old • detailed resume with projects <u>slidenergy.github.io</u>

Expected position: Full-stack .NET developer.

Professional skills

- Back-end: .net core, C#, ASP.NET, WebApi, async programming, T-SQL, NUnit testing, Entity Framework.
- Front-end: Angular (NgRx, RxJs, TS), JS, HTML, CSS, SASS, WinForms, DevExpress, DevExtreme, Angular Material UI, Blazor
- Tools: NodeJS, JIRA, GIT, MS SQL Server, Azure, Heroku.

I know **English**: reading, correspondence and conversational. I have experience in **teamwork**, **remote work**, **technical support**, **commercial software development** and writing high quality and clean code for the purpose of further support.

I have extensive experience in developing various complex **multi-user** systems from scratch, **authorization and authentication** systems. I can work with relational databases, optimize queries, tables and indexes, build an execution plan. I am able to develop **public APIs** using different approaches and technologies. I have extensive experience in **integrating various systems**. I am able to develop complex **frontend**: SPA, desktop applications. I used React, ReactNative, GraphQL, AngularJs In my hobby projects and I follow modern technologies. I am involved in the development of the project and I think in terms of tasks at the level of the entire project.

Work experience - 13 years

LERS AMR Software (2017 – 2021) (www.lers.ru/soft) – Senior Full-stack .NET Developer

- I was responsible for all web development at the company, for the choice of technologies and development vectors. I set tasks and controlled their implementation, did code review.
- I have developed a web application from scratch in Angular to replace the legacy project. The new app is a significant part of the company's core product along with the desktop and mobile app. I was promoting the idea of replacing them with a web application. I have developed an ORM-like core for server queries and caching. I implemented code-style, unit tests, reactive programming, state management, adapted the project for building a mobile application using Cordova, organized and configured the development process.
- I was participating in the development of new server functionality (.net core). I started implementing and contributed a lot to the development of the OpenApi REST API on the server.

LERS MANAGER Company (2013 - 2017) (www.lers.ru/soft) - Middle Full-stack .NET Developer

- I participated in the development of all components of the main software complext of the company for dispatch system and metering of energy consumption, including the development of a server(.NET), database (MS SQL), client application (WinForms). Our team has created the best solution for energy accounting in the CIS counties with great potential for entering the international market.
- I have contributed a lot to the design and development of a framework for integration with other systems. I have designed and developed a public REST API, implemented the the OpenApi specification.
- I was the first to start transition into .net core and angular projects in the company. I study technologies on new and hobby projects: Unit testing, AngularJS, EntityFramework, Angular.
- I have designed and developed new product activation system by internet instead of the old offline one with license key verification. I accepted for support and further development a product for the

- work of the sales department with licensing of the main product. For several years I increased its functionality several times. I have developed a web interface for dealers and technical support.
- I have designed and developed a system for recording, storing and analyzing telemetry data: server (.net core, Entity Framework), frontend (Angular, DevExtreme). I have done deep work with optimizing SQL scripts, tables and indexes, building an execution plan, since the queries were processing large amounts of data.
- At the same time, I provided technical support to users in the CIS countries, wrote documentation, its allowed me to improve my soft-skills.

Energy and resource saving company (2011 - 2013) - Full-stack .NET Developer

- I have developed a unique product for configuring devices and modems, its downloads by customers of competitive products exceeded the download of the main product.
- I have developed many plugins and modules for integration with other systems, a public api service, which allowed clients of other programs to switch to our product.
- I have developed a new web application for a large system from scratch (ASP.NET). The development included a completely frontend, partly a server and a database.
- I refactor the modules of the existing system, which made it possible to simplify the system itself for further development.
- All of the above actions led to several-fold increase in sales.

Neorise LTD (2011, 6 months) - Middle Full-stack .NET Developer, freelance

- I participated in the foreign development of a car service automation system. I have developed a number of modules affecting the client application (DevExpress), server, database (MS SQL).
- I have developed a web application for scheduling mechanics tasks (WebApi, JQuery).
- I communicated with the customer at all stages of development in English.

MPB Intersectoral information-analytical center (2009 - 2011) - Full-stack .NET Developer

- I participated in the development, maintenance of a unified medical information system and integration in all municipal healthcare institutions in Khabarovsk.
- I have written and optimized SQL queries, designed a database (MS SQL 1000 tables).
- I have designed and developed a system for creating queries for preferential medicines and integration it into Khabarovsk's healthcare institutions (.NET, DevExpress).
- I provided technical support for users of Khabarovsk healthcare institutions.

My projects

- I have developed a multi-user personal finance accounting system that, in automatic or manual mode imports information from banking systems (10+). It leads analytics and builds a financial report. https://github.com/slidenergy/slidfinance-backend
- I have developed a cryptocurrency trading robot based on the source codes of a distributed trading exchange. During working, I figured out how React and blockchain work.
- I mentor in my spare time and teach computer science and programming to teenagers.

Education - 7 years

Master degree: Informatics and computer engineering (2009-2011)
Pacific National University, Russia, Khabarovsk city

Software Engineer: Software (2004-2009)
Khabarovsk State Technical University, Russia, Khabarovsk city